You want to move to a two-person room?
Yeah. I'll need meals for two as well.
You're okay with a double, right?
What? Yeah, that's fine.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Huh..
I guess it's a little bigger
than my previous room.
She seems nervous, or rather...
Why don't you put your stuff down?
Yes, Master.
Is she a little scared?
Your ears...
Yes?
Can I touch them?
Yes, Master.
This is just friendly physical contact.
Physical contact between
friends is important.
Don't get any weird ideas.
Suppress your urges, suppress your
urges, suppress your urges...
Crap, I'm addicted.
So cute.
Um, excuse me.
What is it?
Shall I continue calling you Master?
M-a-s-t-e-r!
Roxanne!
Crap. Why am I trying to scare her even more?
Anyway, there's only one
bed in this room, huh?
What?
You're the one who requested that.
So that's what he meant by "double."
He would've said "twin"
if there were two beds.
You're okay with a double, right?
He knew what he was doing.
Good job.
So that's why she's scared.
Roxanne.
What is it, Master?
You wouldn't believe me if I told
you how far away my homeland is.
Is that right?
Yeah. So I'm not really familiar
with what's considered normal here.
I'd appreciate it if you could teach me.
Understood.
Also, you may have heard that
I'll be bringing you into the labyrinth
with me, so keep that in mind.
You can count on me.
I believe I can be useful to you in battle.
You're rather confident.
Roxanne, where are your shoes?
I don't have any.
What? You've been barefoot?
While we were walking outside, too?
Yes?
I totally didn't notice.
Why don't you wear these for now?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Well? They're not too big, are they?
It's all right.
Equipment is made to fit the wearer.
Is that normal here?
Yes. Thank you, Master.
I'll treasure my first gift from you.
Of course she tensed up.
But she doesn't seem to be resisting.
Maybe it's because she's
accepted her fate as a slave,
but I don't know how she really feels.
But still...
I'm not letting you get away.
Yes, Master.
For your equipment,
you can use one of the swords I have,
but what about protective gear?
I don't mind using your spare equipment.
Do you have a shield?
Come to think of it, I don't.
Then I'd like one wooden shield, please.
A wooden shield, huh?
Stare...
She's staring really intently.
I'm glad she's taking this seriously, but...
Identify
Wooden
Shield
Skill Slot
Empty
Identify
Wooden
Shield
Skill Slot
Empty
Identify
Wooden
Shield
Skill Slot
Identify
Wooden
Shield
Skill Slot
Empty
Identify
Wooden
Shield
Skill Slot
Empty
This one, this one, and
this one are good products.
You can tell?
Yeah.
She's really particular about this.
I'd like this one, please.
All right. Onto the next item, then.
We'd like these, please.
Thank you.
A set of protective equipment, olive oil,
canteens, backpacks, socks, towels,
koichi fruit, and shukure branches.
We bought everything we need.
Yes, Master.
That just leaves...
I threw out the cloak I bought before
because it was covered in blood.
Do we really need these?
They're good to have on rainy days.
I see. In that case, I'll get this one.
Roxanne, you can choose
one to your liking, too.
Are you sure?
Stare...
This is gonna take a while.
Not that it matters.
She's pretty and cute.
I'm happy to pass the time watching her.
Master.
Hm?
Which one do you prefer?
I'm being tested here?
If she's asking me, then she
probably already has her answer.
If I choose wrong, I'll lose her trust.
"The cheaper one" is definitely
not the right answer.
Think. Think, Michio.
Well...
She's been carrying that one for a while.
She must've been holding onto
it because she liked it.
In that case...
This one is looser and more stylish.
It's a delicate and subdued color, too.
Is that right?
Did I get it wrong?
This one is better made,
but the color is a bit heavy.
But you're right.
Now that you mention it,
a subdued color could be good.
I see. She was having trouble deciding
between better quality or better color.
Very well. I'll get this one.
I passed the test.
Is there anything else you need?
No, nothing else.
If there's anything you need, don't be shy.
Besides, today's a special day to remember.
In that case, may I purchase
some undergarments?
Undergarments?
Does she mean underwear?!
No, no. This world doesn't have
that kind of bras or panties.
I actually only have the
ones I'm wearing right now.
Then you'll need a spare
set, too. Get two.
Yes, Master. Thank you.
Now we've bought everything, right?
Yes, Master.
Then, let's head back to the inn.
You can have a seat.
Yes, Master.
Not on the floor.
Come here.
But that's your bed, Master.
Don't worry about it.
You'll be sleeping here, too.
I shall use the bed while
accepting your affection,
but I don't mind sleeping on the floor.
Is that normal in this world?
I've heard that's what some masters do.
Then, I'll pass. It seems cold
and kind of a hassle.
Let's sleep together on the bed.
Yes, Master.
Um...
There's still some daylight left.
I'll maintain our equipment.
Oh, yeah?
Well?
It's not bad.
Then...
That said, it's not good either.
You're entrusting your
life to your equipment.
You should keep it properly maintained.
I figured she would be,
but she's particular about the
condition of our equipment, too.
Um...
Hm?
Since you bought new undergarments for me,
I'd like to use my old ones as rags
for maintaining our equipment.
Yeah, that's fine.
Um...
Please feel free to go eat while
I'm performing maintenance.
What? No, let's eat together.
But...
You don't want to?
Oh, no. I didn't say that.
Then, that's what we'll do.
All right, then.
Excuse me.
Oh, right. Her old undergarments are
the ones she's wearing right now.
Uh, sorry. Don't mind me.
If anything, I should try to be considerate.
But I can't help looking at her.
Of course she'd notice me looking.
She's got a tail.
So it does grow out of her tailbone.
I'll have to touch it later.
Error
Image cannot be displayed due to nudity.
That was quick. I guess we
can save the fun for later.
So this is why you bought olive oil.
This will keep it good as new forever.
Does not maintaining your
equipment lower its performance?
If it doesn't feel good to use,
then you can't operate at peak performance.
You mean it's all psychological, then?
I brought you some hot water.
You want enough for two, right?
Yeah.
Finally, the time has come.
Don't rush. There's a proper
order to things. First...
Could you scrub my back, Roxanne?
Yes, Master.
Don't be embarrassed.
We're all naked when we come into this world.
And besides, if I get embarrassed,
it'll make Roxanne nervous.
Go ahead.
Is this the right amount of pressure?
Yeah, it feels good.
If I could be a little greedy,
I wish I could bathe in the
water up to my shoulders.
In the water?
Yeah. Roxanne, are you familiar with baths?
Yes, Master.
But it's difficult to get a
large amount of hot water.
I doubt many people take baths
unless they're very wealthy.
Huh, I see.
She didn't react much to
seeing the front of my body.
That makes me kind of sad.
Now it's your turn, Roxanne.
Yes, Master.
I feel like I shouldn't watch.
Um, since I'm a wolfkin,
I may be a bit hairy.
Oh, really?
This is an act of violence!
Projectile weapons!
That's gotta be against the rules!
E-Especially my back...
She doesn't need to hide anything.
Not that she's managing to hide anything.
Yeah, this is all right.
Master?
Oh, right.
This isn't her hair. It's growing
directly out of her back.
It's so thick and soft. I like it.
Thank you.
I don't think I can ask you
to scrub my back after all.
It's all right. It'll be faster this way.
I want to see those peaks
sway as I scrub her back.
I must see them. No, the privilege
of seeing them will be mine.
Viva Roxanne!
But just looking at them isn't enough.
I must worship them.
I must worship these swelling peaks.
What?
Nothing.
I touched them. I'm finally touching
them with my own two hands.
I can feel how soft they
are, even through the cloth.
They're so freaking soft.
But they're also bouncy,
and my fingers sink into
them at the lightest touch.
They don't fit in my hands,
and a single touch isn't enough
to get the full picture.
Their texture is like a cross between
marshmallows and water balloons.
They're amazing.
Crap, did I spend too long touching them?
Um, is it all right to wash your tail?
Yes, Master. I'll do it myself.
It's fine.
There doesn't seem to be a core.
Can you move this?
It's difficult to move just my tail.
If I do this...
then it's not impossible.
Roxanne is shaking her
hips right in front of me!
This isn't fair!
Also, sometimes it moves
involuntarily when I'm happy.
I see. Then we'd better keep your
tail moving as much as possible.
Yes, Master.
Thank you, Master.
Why don't we perform an experiment?
How is it?
That feels good, Master.
With two of us, we can wash our heads, too.
Master, shall I wash yours, as well?
Yes, please.
This feels great.
I hadn't washed my hair
once yet since coming here.
This is paradise!
No, no. I should focus on having
my hair washed right now.
Stay calm.
Master, did I miss any spots?
No, that's enough.
There was another ambush waiting for me here!
This is great. I wish I
could stare at them forever.
Wait, no! Why am I being satisfied
by just looking at them?
Now is the time to take one big step forward.
Roxanne.
Um, uh...
I'll put these clothes on.
Huh?
Wouldn't you be pleased if I wore this?
What did that slave trader teach her?
You can wear that another time.
Yes, Master.
Remove your undergarments.
Is this all right?
Excuse me.
Now Roxanne is in her birthday suit.
She closed her eyes.
Which means this is all right, right?
I'm kissing her.
I'm kissing a beautiful girl.
I wish I could be more aggressive,
but I need to be patient.
I can't use tongue from the get-go.
At least, I think I've heard people say that.
Gently, like a tender invitation.
Don't scare her.
From now on, I want you to kiss
me before we go to bed at night
and when we wake up in the morning.
Yes, Master.
One more time.
I'll be a little more
aggressive the second time.
Good. She's accepting my advances.
I don't want to stop, but I want
to savor other parts of her, too.
This time I want to get a
proper look at Roxanne's breasts,
not just steal glances at them.
May I touch them?
Go ahead.
So soft.
It's far smoother than touching
them through fabric,
and they cling to my hands a little.
My hands sink into them forever,
but they bounce right back
into their original shape.
This is bliss.
Error
Image cannot be displayed due to nudity.
I'd only tasted the fruit
of Roxanne in my dreams,
but they're even juicier than I imagined.
Roxanne.
Can I?
Master, I'm gonna...
Master...
It's morning.
I never knew the weight of another
person could feel so comfortable.
I can't believe I'm getting to
experience a morning like this.
Oh, right.
I told her to kiss me before
bed and when I wake up.
She's faithfully following my instructions.
Good morning, Master.
Good morning, Roxanne.
Whoops.
I responded to her touch.
I hate to get out of bed, but
we can have fun again tonight.
For now...
Shall we head into the labyrinth, Roxanne?
Yes, Master.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem